golden.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy | Golden

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their **"Personally Identifiable Information" (PII)** is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our site?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site.

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver right type of content
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products

How do we protect your information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via

**Secure Socket Layer (SSL)** technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

For your convenience we may store your credit card information longer than 30 days in order to expedite future orders, and to automate the billing process.

Do we use "cookies"?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use "cookies" to:

  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?

We honor **Do Not Track** signals and **Do Not Track** , plant cookies, or use advertising when a **Do Not Track (DNT)** browser mechanism is in place.

Does our site allow 3rd party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking.

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the **Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)** puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

Golden does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

CAN SPAM Act

The **CAN-SPAM Act** is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Golden by contacting us at privacy@golden.co.

Changes to this Statement

Golden will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Golden encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Golden is protecting your information.

Contact Information

Golden welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Golden has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Golden at:

  * Golden Recursion Inc.
  * 30 7th Street
  * San Francisco, CA 94103
  * Phone: 415-779-4053
  * Email: [privacy@golden.co](mailto:privacy@golden.co)
